

FADHLAN ASSIDIKI RUDFA

+6282177409322 | alan.assidiki@gmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/fadhlanassidikirudfa/ | https://www.behance.net/fadhlanassidiki

Yogyakarta, Indonesia 55191

I am a fresh graduate in Informatics Engineering with a focus on UI/UX Design. I have professional experience as a Front-end Developer & UI/UX Designer and have succeeded in increasing user satisfaction by developing the UI/UX of the company website. During my college years, I actively engaged in UI/UX design training and courses, where I developed my skills in user research, wireframing, prototyping, and interaction design.

Work Experiences

Biro Akademik & Admisi Universitas Ahmad Dahlan -

Sep 2022 - Present

Yogyakarta

Class Manager Intern

- Managed data and information of students from 60+ study programs related to academic and administrative activities.
- Ensure that room usage schedules and class schedules align with the needs of the campus, as well as managing data related to rooms and class schedules.
- Providing support for academic and administrative related issues.

Ombein Indonesia - Yogyakarta

Mar 2022 - Jun 2022

Head of Crew Outlet

- Responsible for 4 other of crew members, including organizing work schedules, and monitoring employee performance.
- Increased monthly income by 16% through ShopeeFood mobile application.
- Earned 100+ positive comments from costumer reviewing the shop on GoFood, GrabFood, and ShopeeFood.
- · Managed inventory levels and ordering of supplies, ensuring that the store is well-stocked.
- Analyzed outlet finances, ensuring accurate financial records, and creating clear and organized financial reports.

PMI Kabupaten Seluma - Bengkulu

Feb 2020 - Jul 2020

Front-end Developer Intern

- Created prototypes and designed 5+ visual interfaces for PMI Kabupaten Seluma's profile website.
- Collaborated with 2 cross-functional teams on Product UX Dashboard, login page, and homepage.
- Developed responsive and user-friendly web pages.
- Ensure that the end-product meets both technical and business requirements.
- Increased user satisfaction by over 85% and perceived findability of information by over 80%.

Education

Universitas Ahmad Dahlan - Yogyakarta

Aug 2018 - Dec 2022

Bachelor Degree in Informatics Engineering, 3.31/4.00

· Relevant Coursework: Data Structures and Algorithms, Web and Mobile Application Development.

MySkill UI/UX Research and Design: Fullstack Intensive Bootcamp - Yogyakarta

Mar 2023 - May 2023

Certificate in UI/UX Research and Design

• Learn User Interfaces Design, User Research, Prototyping, and more.

Skills & Certification

- **Skills**: User Interface Design, User Research, Web Design, Interaction Design, Usability Testing, Figma (Software), Problem solving, Communication skills, Knowledge of programming languages, Collaboration.
- Language: English (Intermediate)
- **Certification**: Certificate of Best Final Project MySkill(2023), UI/UX Design Essentials Udemy(2023), Complete UI Design BuildWith Angga(2023), UX Foundations Research Linkedin Learning(2023), Kickstart UI/UX Designer Rakamin(2023).